[
    { "question" : "essere", "answer" : "to be", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɛssere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "avere", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "/aˈvere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "fare", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dire", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "andare", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/anˈdare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "venire", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/veˈnire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vedere", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/veˈdere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "sentire", "answer" : "to hear", "pronunciation" : "/senˈtire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "pensare", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/penˈsare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "capire", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈpire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "parlare", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/parˈlare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "mangiare", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "/manˈdʒare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "bere", "answer" : "to drink", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "studiare", "answer" : "to study", "pronunciation" : "/stuˈdjare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "lavorare", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/lavoˈrare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "chiedere", "answer" : "to ask", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkjedere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "sapere", "answer" : "to know (fact)", "pronunciation" : "/saˈpere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "conoscere", "answer" : "to know (person", "pronunciation" : "/konˈtʃezere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "potere", "answer" : "can", "pronunciation" : "/poˈtere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dovere", "answer" : "must", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdovere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "volere", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/voˈlere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "prendere", "answer" : "to take", "pronunciation" : "/prenˈdere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "lasciare", "answer" : "to leave", "pronunciation" : "/laʃˈʃare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "guardare", "answer" : "to watch", "pronunciation" : "/ɡwarˈdare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "aspettare", "answer" : "to wait for", "pronunciation" : "/aspetˈtare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "uscire", "answer" : "to go out", "pronunciation" : "/uˈʃire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "entrare", "answer" : "to enter", "pronunciation" : "/enˈtrare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dimenticare", "answer" : "to forget", "pronunciation" : "/dimenˈtikare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ricordare", "answer" : "to remember", "pronunciation" : "/rikorˈdare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "trovare", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "/troˈvare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "conoscere", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "/konˈtʃezere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "incontrare", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "/inkonˈtrare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "rimanere", "answer" : "to remain", "pronunciation" : "/rimaˈnere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "camminare", "answer" : "to walk", "pronunciation" : "/kammiˈnare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "correre", "answer" : "to run", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkorrere/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "nuotare", "answer" : "to swim", "pronunciation" : "/nwoˈtare/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dormire", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "/dorˈmire/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "svegliarsi", "answer" : "to wake up", "pronunciation" : "/sveʎˈʎarsi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vestirsi", "answer" : "to get dressed", "pronunciation" : "/vestirˈsi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "spogliarsi", "answer" : "to get undressed", "pronunciation" : "/spoʎˈʎarsi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "lavarsi", "answer" : "to wash oneself", "pronunciation" : "/laˈvarsi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "pettinarsi", "answer" : "to comb one's hair", "pronunciation" : "/pettiˈnarsi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "acqua", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/ˈakkwa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "albero", "answer" : "tree", "pronunciation" : "/ˈalbero/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "amico", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "/aˈmiko/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "animale", "answer" : "animal", "pronunciation" : "/aniˈmale/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "anno", "answer" : "year", "pronunciation" : "/ˈanno/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "armadio", "answer" : "wardrobe", "pronunciation" : "/arˈmadjo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "auto", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "/ˈauto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "bicchiere", "answer" : "glass", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbikkjere/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "casa", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkaza/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "cellulare", "answer" : "cell phone", "pronunciation" : "/tʃelluˈlare/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "centro", "answer" : "center", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃentro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "chiesa", "answer" : "church", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkjɛza/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "città", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃitta/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "cibo", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃibo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "città", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃitta/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "cioccolato", "answer" : "chocolate", "pronunciation" : "/tʃokkoˈlato/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "cognome", "answer" : "surname", "pronunciation" : "/koɲˈɲome/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "computer", "answer" : "computer", "pronunciation" : "/komˈputer/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "lavoro", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "/laˈvoro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "libro", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "/ˈlibro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "maglia", "answer" : "sweater", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmaʎʎa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "mare", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmare/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "medicina", "answer" : "medicine", "pronunciation" : "/mediˈtʃina/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "mercato", "answer" : "market", "pronunciation" : "/merˈkato/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "metro", "answer" : "subway", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmetro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "montagna", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "/monˈtaɲɲa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "museo", "answer" : "museum", "pronunciation" : "/muˈzɛo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "musica", "answer" : "music", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmuzika/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "notte", "answer" : "night", "pronunciation" : "/ˈnɔtte/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ombrello", "answer" : "umbrella", "pronunciation" : "/omˈbrɛllo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "oro", "answer" : "gold", "pronunciation" : "/ˈoro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "palla", "answer" : "ball", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpalla/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pane", "answer" : "bread", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpane/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "papa", "answer" : "potato", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpapa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "parco", "answer" : "park", "pronunciation" : "/ˈparko/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pasto", "answer" : "meal", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpasto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "penna", "answer" : "pen", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpenna/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "piazza", "answer" : "square", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpjattsa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pianta", "answer" : "plant", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpjanta/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pizza", "answer" : "pizza", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpittsa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pollo", "answer" : "chicken", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpollo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "portafoglio", "answer" : "wallet", "pronunciation" : "/portaˈfoʎʎo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pranzo", "answer" : "lunch", "pronunciation" : "/ˈprantso/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "problema", "answer" : "problem", "pronunciation" : "/proˈblema/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "progetto", "answer" : "project", "pronunciation" : "/proˈdʒetto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "provincia", "answer" : "province", "pronunciation" : "/provinˈʧia/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ragazzo", "answer" : "boy", "pronunciation" : "/raˈɡattso/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ragazza", "answer" : "girl", "pronunciation" : "/raˈɡattsa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "accogliente", "answer" : "cozy", "pronunciation" : "/akkoʎˈʎɛnte/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "affidabile", "answer" : "reliable", "pronunciation" : "/affiˈdabile/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "affettuoso", "answer" : "affectionate", "pronunciation" : "/affetˈtuoso/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "aggiornato", "answer" : "up-to-date", "pronunciation" : "/addʒorˈnato/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "allegra", "answer" : "cheerful", "pronunciation" : "/alˈlɛɡra/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "amabile", "answer" : "pleasant", "pronunciation" : "/aˈmabile/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ambizioso", "answer" : "ambitious", "pronunciation" : "/ambiˈtsjozjo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "amichevole", "answer" : "friendly", "pronunciation" : "/amikeˈvole/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "antipatico", "answer" : "unpleasant", "pronunciation" : "/antipaˈtiko/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "appassionato", "answer" : "passionate", "pronunciation" : "/appasːjoˈnato/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "attraente", "answer" : "attractive", "pronunciation" : "/attraˈɛnte/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "autentico", "answer" : "authentic", "pronunciation" : "/autenˈtiko/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "brillante", "answer" : "brilliant", "pronunciation" : "/briˈljante/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "buono", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/buˈono/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "calmo", "answer" : "calm", "pronunciation" : "/kalmo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "capace", "answer" : "capable", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈpatʃe/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "carino", "answer" : "cute", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈrino/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "chiaro", "answer" : "clear", "pronunciation" : "/kjaro/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "colorato", "answer" : "colorful", "pronunciation" : "/koloˈrato/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "comodo", "answer" : "comfortable", "pronunciation" : "/koˈmodo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "competente", "answer" : "competent", "pronunciation" : "/kompeˈtente/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "confortevole", "answer" : "comfortable", "pronunciation" : "/konforˈtevole/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "confuso", "answer" : "confused", "pronunciation" : "/konˈfuzo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "coraggioso", "answer" : "brave", "pronunciation" : "/koradˈdʒoso/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "cortese", "answer" : "polite", "pronunciation" : "/korˈtese/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "creativo", "answer" : "creative", "pronunciation" : "/kreaˈtivo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "curioso", "answer" : "curious", "pronunciation" : "/kuˈrjozo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "deciso", "answer" : "decisive", "pronunciation" : "/deˈtʃizo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "delicato", "answer" : "delicate", "pronunciation" : "/deliˈkato/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "disponibile", "answer" : "available", "pronunciation" : "/dispoˈnibile/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "divertente", "answer" : "entertaining", "pronunciation" : "/diverˈtente/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "dolce", "answer" : "sweet", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdoltʃe/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "elegante", "answer" : "elegant", "pronunciation" : "/eleˈɡante/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "emotivo", "answer" : "emotional", "pronunciation" : "/emoˈtivo/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "energico", "answer" : "energetic", "pronunciation" : "/enerˈdʒiko/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "equilibrato", "answer" : "balanced", "pronunciation" : "/ekwiliˈbrato/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "esperto", "answer" : "expert", "pronunciation" : "/esˈperto/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "adesso", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/aˈdɛsso/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a destra", "answer" : "to the right", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈdestra/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a fianco", "answer" : "next to", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈfjaŋko/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a lungo", "answer" : "for a long time", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈluŋɡo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a mano", "answer" : "by hand", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈmano/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a meno", "answer" : "at least", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈmɛno/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a sinistra", "answer" : "to the left", "pronunciation" : "/a ˈsinistra/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "allora", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/alˈlora/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "altrove", "answer" : "elsewhere", "pronunciation" : "/alˈtrove/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "anche", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/ˈanke/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ancora", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/anˈkora/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "appena", "answer" : "just", "pronunciation" : "/apˈpena/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "assai", "answer" : "quite", "pronunciation" : "/asˈsai/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ben", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "/ben/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "bravo", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbravo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "certo", "answer" : "certainly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃerto/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "chi", "answer" : "who", "pronunciation" : "/ki/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "come", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkome/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "così", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/koˈsi/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "da allora", "answer" : "since then", "pronunciation" : "/da alˈlora/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dappertutto", "answer" : "everywhere", "pronunciation" : "/dapperˈtutto/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "davanti", "answer" : "in front of", "pronunciation" : "/daˈvanti/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "del tutto", "answer" : "completely", "pronunciation" : "/del ˈtutto/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dentro", "answer" : "inside", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdentro/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "di nuovo", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "/di ˈnwɔvo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "di solito", "answer" : "usually", "pronunciation" : "/di soˈlito/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dietro", "answer" : "behind", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdjetro/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "domani", "answer" : "tomorrow", "pronunciation" : "/doˈmani/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dopo", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdopo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dove", "answer" : "where", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdove/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dunque", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdunkwe/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ecco", "answer" : "here is", "pronunciation" : "/ˈekko/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "eppure", "answer" : "yet", "pronunciation" : "/epˈpure/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "forse", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/ˈforse/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "fra poco", "answer" : "soon", "pronunciation" : "/fra ˈpɔko/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "fuori", "answer" : "outside", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfwɔri/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "già", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdʒa/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ieri", "answer" : "yesterday", "pronunciation" : "/jeˈri/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "in alto", "answer" : "up", "pronunciation" : "/in ˈalto/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "in basso", "answer" : "down", "pronunciation" : "/in ˈbasso/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "insieme", "answer" : "together", "pronunciation" : "/inˈsjɛme/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "laggiù", "answer" : "down there", "pronunciation" : "/ladˈdʒu/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "lassù", "answer" : "up there", "pronunciation" : "/laˈsu/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "affinché", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/afˈfinke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "anche se", "answer" : "even if", "pronunciation" : "/ˈanke se/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "appena", "answer" : "as soon as", "pronunciation" : "/apˈpena/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "benché", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbenke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "cioè", "answer" : "that is", "pronunciation" : "/ˈtʃɔe/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "comunque", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/koˈmunque/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "con", "answer" : "with", "pronunciation" : "/kon/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "cosicché", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/koˈsikke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "così", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/koˈsi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "da", "answer" : "from", "pronunciation" : "/da/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "dato che", "answer" : "given that", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdato ke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "del resto", "answer" : "moreover", "pronunciation" : "/del ˈresto/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "difatti", "answer" : "in fact", "pronunciation" : "/diˈfatti/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "dopo che", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/ˈdopo ke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "e", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/e/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "eppure", "answer" : "yet", "pronunciation" : "/epˈpure/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "finché", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfinke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "giacché", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/dʒakˈke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "in quanto", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/in ˈkwanto/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "infatti", "answer" : "in fact", "pronunciation" : "/inˈfatti/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "innanzitutto", "answer" : "first of all", "pronunciation" : "/innanˈdzitutto/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ma", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/ma/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "magari", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/maˈɡari/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "mentre", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmentre/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "né", "answer" : "neither", "pronunciation" : "/ne/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "nondimeno", "answer" : "nevertheless", "pronunciation" : "/nondiˈmeno/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "nonostante", "answer" : "despite", "pronunciation" : "/nononˈstante/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "o", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/o/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "oppure", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "/opˈpure/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ovunque", "answer" : "wherever", "pronunciation" : "/oˈvunque/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "perciò", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/perˈtʃio/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "perché", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/perˈke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "piuttosto", "answer" : "rather", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpjuttosto/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "poiché", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/poiˈke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "qualora", "answer" : "in case", "pronunciation" : "/kwaˈlora/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "quando", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkwando/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "quindi", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkwindi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "sennò", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsenno/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "sicché", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsikke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "siccome", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsikkome/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "sinché", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsinke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "tuttavia", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/tuttaˈvia/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ugualmente", "answer" : "equally", "pronunciation" : "/uɡwaˈlmente/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "un po'", "answer" : "a little bit", "pronunciation" : "/un ˈpɔ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]